{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734479845","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734479845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734480821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734480820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734483778","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734483777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734484322","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734484322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734484985","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734484984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734489175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734489175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734490111","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734490110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734493846","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734493845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734494637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734494636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734495626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734495625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734499451","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734499451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734500414","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734500413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734503306","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734503306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734503838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734503838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734504482","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734504481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734508567","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734508566"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734509492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734509491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734513106","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734513106"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734513888","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734513888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734514862","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734514862"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734518147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734518146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734518228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734518228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734618214","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734618213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 5f4dab80-21b1-4c11-b090-4dc9a3d6dbac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734618339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734618339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 18249271-4efe-4270-bcdf-fc117de49e00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_20"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulitishika sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734644279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734644279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734664734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734664734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734667932","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734667932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734686434","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734686434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734688806","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734688805"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734709405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734709405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734736956","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734736954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734737031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734737030"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 26619c5b-7dfa-4275-a6b9-1f25095c462a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734767517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734767517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734788282","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734788282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734807290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734807289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734809833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734809832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734812273","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734812272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734833421","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734833421"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734860926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734860924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734861015","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734861015"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bd01087b-9cb5-4e65-9343-be9f6ca04735"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734890118","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734890118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734910625","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734910625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734928999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734928999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734949600","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734949600"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734977066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734977064"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734977173","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734977173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PENDO"," userResponse":" PENDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.show.94","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734983828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734983828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.mc.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734990689","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734990689"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" eddf0e03-0754-43c4-95f4-c26d8b9f7585"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_17"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je umefahamu kwa nini ninampenda ng'ombe wetu Pendo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543734999321","data":{"timestamp":" 1543734999321"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_n-f-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735004285","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735004285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_l-y-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735015266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735015266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-u-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735020532","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735020531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_f-i-y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735024837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735024837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-e-l"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735029341","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735029341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-k-b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735039638","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735039638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-k-b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735049636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735049636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_d-i-a"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735060679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735060679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-z-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735064969","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735064968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_t-i-d"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735070439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735070439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735076208","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735076207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735088468","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735088468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735110629","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735110629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 757579c2-d6c2-4b54-a562-275fa90e5502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_I..I.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.95"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_i_r-i-a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735110682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735110681"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ec740c66-e757-4c18-a4a8-a8331bf385da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hi ni hadithi ya Mlinzi na chekechea yake ya wanyama mayatima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEKECHEA"," userResponse":" CHEKECHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735131171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735131171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_f_i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735137840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735137840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_e_i_v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735144505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735144504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_y_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735151182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735151181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_l"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735158723","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735158723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_e_l"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735165375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735165374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_l_i"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735172033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735172032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_o_p"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735179512","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735179512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_o_p"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735186213","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735186211"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_f_b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735192894","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735192893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_g_p_i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735199569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735199569"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735207108","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735207108"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_a_p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:I..I.all.10.rand.say.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735216112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735216112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_i_a_p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.mc.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735224474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735224474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_i_a_p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735232381","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735232381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" bc65edd7-c872-4015-a109-9ff62e2704c9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_I..I.all.10.rand.say.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_i_a_p"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735293317","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735293317"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mlango-msituni-bwana-bado"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" bwana"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735298800","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735298800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mlango-msituni-bwana-bado"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" bado"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735304403","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735304403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mlango-msituni-bwana-bado"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735331766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735331766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_mahali-hebu-msituni-bwana"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735357001","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735357001"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jitu_kabisa-jitu-bibi-vizuri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jitu"," userResponse":" kabisa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735359918","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735359918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jitu_kabisa-jitu-bibi-vizuri"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" jitu"," userResponse":" jitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735378041","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735378041"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msitu_msitu-mfuko-vizuri-sokoni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msitu"," userResponse":" vizuri"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735386612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735386612"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msitu_msitu-mfuko-vizuri-sokoni"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msitu"," userResponse":" msitu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735418402","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735418402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" msituni_tu-msituni-zawadi-mrembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" msituni"," userResponse":" msituni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735427875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735427873"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" msituni_tu-msituni-zawadi-mrembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735427985","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735427985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2604f9af-9e75-4e11-b816-1fd7da760dd7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliamini kuwa ameliwa na ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543735450344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543735450343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737211346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737211346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::0..10.SD_OFF1_RAND.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737229005","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737229004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737236739","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737236739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737243870","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737243870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737250986","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737250985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.mc.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737256689","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737256688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737262097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737262097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fec72d0d-3722-4f5d-b63d-b670a9a90337"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737275253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737275253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737275757","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737275757"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737276908","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737276908"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737279808","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737279808"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737280545","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737280545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737281141","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737281140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737284003","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737284003"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737284713","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737284712"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737285248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737285248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737285461","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737285461"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737286345","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737286342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737289084","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737289084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737289630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737289629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737290680","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737290679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737293404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737293403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737294155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737294155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737294751","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737294751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737297612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737297611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737298351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737298351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737298849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737298849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737299061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737299060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737299766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737299766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737303120","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737303119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737303724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737303723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737305375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737305375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" ALIPALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737306176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737306175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737306725","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737306724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737307358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737307358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737310202","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737310201"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737310680","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737310680"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737312396","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737312396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737313162","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737313162"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737313708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737313708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737314278","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737314278"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737317306","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737317306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737317574","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737317573"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737318283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737318283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737319103","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737319103"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737319799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737319799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737320380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737320379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737321131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737321131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737321895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737321894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737322369","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737322368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZO"," userResponse":" HIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737322910","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737322910"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737325328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737325328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737325631","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737325631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737326180","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737326180"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737327143","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737327140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737327734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737327734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVUNA"," userResponse":" TULIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737328462","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737328461"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737328780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737328780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737329670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737329669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737332975","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737332975"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737333494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737333494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737333727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737333727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737334632","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737334632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737335569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737335569"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737336553","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737336552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737336757","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737336757"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737337611","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737337611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737340283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737340283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737340790","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737340790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737340989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737340988"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737341662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737341662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737342686","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737342685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737343671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737343671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737343944","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737343943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737344649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737344649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737347427","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737347427"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737347931","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737347931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737349072","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737349072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543737349936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543737349936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fa8b5070-9563-443b-8a6a-a7d68fc0d9e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747126578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747126578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747127081","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747127081"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747128224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747128224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747131056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747131055"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747131769","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747131769"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747132343","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747132343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747135132","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747135132"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747135825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747135825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747136339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747136339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747136543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747136543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747137396","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747137396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747140089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747140089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747140623","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747140623"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747141667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747141666"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747144355","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747144355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747145068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747145068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747145641","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747145641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747148452","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747148452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747149156","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747149156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747149641","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747149640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747149843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747149843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747150527","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747150527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani ndogo ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747153763","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747153763"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747154356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747154356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747155999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747155999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPALILIA"," userResponse":" ALIPALILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747156792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747156792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747157325","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747157325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747157939","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747157939"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipalilia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747160740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747160739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747161213","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747161213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747162916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747162916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," userResponse":" ALINYUNYIZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747163669","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747163669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747164203","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747164203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747164767","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747164767"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba yangu alinyunyizia bustani zote mbili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747167700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747167700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747167963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747167963"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747168667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747168667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747169479","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747169479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747170172","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747170172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747170735","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747170735"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747171469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747171469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747172224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747172224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747172688","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747172688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZO"," userResponse":" HIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747173221","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747173221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na wazazi wangu tulifanya kazi katika bustani hizo ndogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747175623","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747175623"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747175917","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747175917"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747176462","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747176462"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747177405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747177405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747177969","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747177969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIVUNA"," userResponse":" TULIVUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747178683","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747178683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747178996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747178996"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747179880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747179880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na dada yangu tulivuna maua na mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747183132","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747183131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747183653","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747183653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747183881","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747183881"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747184776","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747184776"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747185700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747185700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747186684","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747186684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747186887","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747186887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747187741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747187741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya mbaazi ilizaa magunia ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747190356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747190356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747190859","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747190859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOGO"," userResponse":" NDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747191052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747191052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747191716","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747191716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747192740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747192740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZAA"," userResponse":" ILIZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747193715","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747193714"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAGUNIA"," userResponse":" MAGUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747193978","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747193978"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747194662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747194662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani ndogo ya maua ilizaa magunia ya maua."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747197475","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747197475"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747197979","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747197979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747199123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747199123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama yangu alipanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747202032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747202032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747202756","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747202755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747203387","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747203387"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipanda bustani kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747205844","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747205844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUSTANI"," userResponse":" BUSTANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747206437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747206437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747207701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747207701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYOPANDA"," userResponse":" ALIYOPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747208546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747208545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747208780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747208780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747209644","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747209644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747209976","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747209976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747210097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747210097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" a54f7e6c-e3b1-44dd-ac16-a29811f934e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_21"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bustani kubwa aliyopanda ilikuwa ya mbaazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAAZI"," userResponse":" MBAAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747219855","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747219855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747220229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747220229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747220712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747220712"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747221056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747221056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747221459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747221459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747221932","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747221932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747222156","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747222155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747225342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747225341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747225375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747225374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747226087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747226087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747226480","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747226480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747226774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747226774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747226977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747226977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747227171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747227171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747227485","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747227484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747227708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747227708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747230885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747230885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747231288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747231288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747233770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747233770"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747233973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747233973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747234176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747234176"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747237599","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747237599"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747239406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747239405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747239478","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747239478"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c47ca4ad-59f8-4d2a-9e80-451d55c3a102"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747258553","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747258553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_0_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747265192","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747265192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1_4_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747272739","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747272739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1_4_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747281783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747281783"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_1_4_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747287964","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747287964"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_0_2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747295406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747295406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_0_2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747304419","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747304419"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_0_2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747310618","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747310618"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_4_3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747318093","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747318093"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_4_3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747327127","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747327126"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_8_4_3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747333323","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747333323"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747340784","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747340784"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747349818","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747349818"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747355997","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747355997"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_2_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747363460","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747363460"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_2_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747372493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747372493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_2_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747378693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747378692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_9_6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747386125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747386125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_9_6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747395160","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747395159"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_9_6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747401342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747401341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_6_5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.asc","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747403730","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747403729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_7_6_5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747446976","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747446976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9fc0520b-de49-4748-92f2-67a1a6c15f07"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.asc"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_7_6_5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747456885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747456884"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747457918","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747457918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747459267","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747459267"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" ANAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747460142","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747460137"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747461077","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747461076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747461667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747461667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747462571","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747462571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747466012","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747466012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747466576","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747466576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747467288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747467288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747467880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747467880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747468061","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747468060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747469294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747469293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747472896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747472896"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747473380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747473380"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747474183","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747474183"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747475147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747475147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" ULIOPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747478471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747478471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747479035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747479035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747479740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747479740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747480314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747480314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747480487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747480487"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747481715","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747481715"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747485380","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747485379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANATANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747486174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747486173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747486894","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747486894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747487977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747487977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747488541","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747488541"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747491919","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747491919"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TUNAJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747492482","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747492482"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747493186","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747493186"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747493760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747493759"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" YAYERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747493933","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747493933"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747495157","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747495157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747499167","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747499167"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747499184","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747499184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747499271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747499270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 1b957743-c319-4789-9a1f-70a9935999f0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" ANAWASALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747508998","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747508998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" edbbf159-2c66-4e0e-9467-5048351ea624"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747514094","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747514094"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" edbbf159-2c66-4e0e-9467-5048351ea624"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-t-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747517269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747517269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" edbbf159-2c66-4e0e-9467-5048351ea624"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747529643","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747529643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" edbbf159-2c66-4e0e-9467-5048351ea624"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747533941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747533941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" edbbf159-2c66-4e0e-9467-5048351ea624"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747559022","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747559022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c812a4c6-4480-4b53-bd56-ac3048ad6414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747563294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747563293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" c812a4c6-4480-4b53-bd56-ac3048ad6414"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.s2s.AV.rise.28"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747572171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747572171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ff8a1b0e-9223-4f0e-a0ee-a54b609faac5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747695318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747695318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_k-y-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747715031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747715031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_k-y-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747725411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747725411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_h-d-j"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747731289","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747731289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-v-m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747734653","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747734653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-t-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747738083","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747738083"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747741276","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747741276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_s-j-t"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747744149","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747744149"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-b-h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747747035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747747035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-e-k"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747750338","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747750338"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_m-j-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747753634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747753634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_v-p-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747759448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747759448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 637f51b7-0586-4b54-93b1-e411f1b4b901"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_J..J.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.97"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_j_v-p-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747772011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747772010"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747772910","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747772910"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TULIENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747773572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747773571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747774191","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747774190"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" SHEREHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747774411","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747774411"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747775164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747775164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" DASARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747778164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747778164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" PAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747779472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747779472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALIMNUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747780080","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747780079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" CHINTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747780856","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747780856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" MIWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747780934","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747780934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747781943","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747781943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" KUPENDEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747784295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747784294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747786069","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747786068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALININUNULIA"," userResponse":" ALININUNULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747786805","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747786805"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747787066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747787065"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747787570","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747787570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747787666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747787666"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747788774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747788774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747790309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747790309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" ILIYONG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747790318","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747790318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AA"," userResponse":" AA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747790843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747790843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747793659","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747793658"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747794742","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747794742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747795652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747795652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747798654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747798653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TUKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747799374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747799373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747799971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747799971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747800956","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747800955"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747801956","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747801956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747802679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747802678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" MKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747803571","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747803571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747806968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747806968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747807627","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747807627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747808170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747808170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747808783","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747808783"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747812017","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747812017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747812873","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747812872"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747814079","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747814079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZUILIWA"," userResponse":" ILIZUILIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747814986","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747814985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747815813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747815813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747815943","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747815943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747816423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747816423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747816647","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747816647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747817296","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747817295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747820006","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747820006"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIA"," userResponse":" NILILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747821468","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747821468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747823635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747823634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747824474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747824474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKULA"," userResponse":" SIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747825171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747825171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747825777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747825777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747826060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747826060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747826929","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747826929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747829952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747829952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747831149","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747831149"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747831471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747831471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747832413","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747832413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747833700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747833700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye usiku ule mwezi ulitokezea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" ULITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747837098","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747837098"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ULIIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747837731","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747837731"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747838207","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747838207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747838684","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747838683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747839182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747839182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747839622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747839622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747839853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747839853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747840473","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747840472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliiangalia kofia yangu pale kwenye mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" MIIBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747843617","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747843617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEZI"," userResponse":" MWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747844590","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747844590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIJARIBU"," userResponse":" ULIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747845475","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747845474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIVAA"," userResponse":" KUIVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747846116","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747846116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747846710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747846710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwezi ulijaribu kuivaa kofia yangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747850293","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747850293"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULITABASAMU"," userResponse":" ULITABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747850655","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747850654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747851839","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747851839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ulitabasamu kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747854505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747854505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747854740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747854740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747855384","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747855384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUDI"," userResponse":" BUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747855817","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747855817"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747857263","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747857263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTABASAMU"," userResponse":" KUTABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747858007","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747858006"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikuwa na budi ila kutabasamu pia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747861171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747861171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747861365","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747861364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747862008","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747862008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747862630","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747862630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747863232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747863232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747864572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747864571"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747865756","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747865756"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747866254","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747866254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747866333","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747866333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:J..J.all.10.rand.say.48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747874760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747874759"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 2c04a650-414a-4ff2-834a-66a20b6d4e0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_24"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baada ya kutoka shule siku iliyofuata mamangu alinipa kofia nyingine nyekundi iliyong'ara mano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747883878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747883878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 914c9d70-4b12-42ee-a636-ff58ae5f3079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-0-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747884149","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747884149"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 914c9d70-4b12-42ee-a636-ff58ae5f3079"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-0-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747896672","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747896672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 0148a117-6828-4472-a86d-9cf33285d5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747899492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747899492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 0148a117-6828-4472-a86d-9cf33285d5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747901110","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747901110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 0148a117-6828-4472-a86d-9cf33285d5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747902239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747902239"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 0148a117-6828-4472-a86d-9cf33285d5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747902356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747902356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 0148a117-6828-4472-a86d-9cf33285d5fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747911985","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747911984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747912223","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747912223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747912673","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747912673"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747913114","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747913114"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747913444","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747913443"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747914254","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747914254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747914853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747914852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747915100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747915100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747915897","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747915897"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747918649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747918648"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747919636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747919636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747920076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747920075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747920272","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747920272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747920866","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747920866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilikuwa kubwa na ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747924041","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747924041"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOA"," userResponse":" ILITOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747924666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747924665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KELELE"," userResponse":" KELELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747925425","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747925425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilitoa kelele sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747928410","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747928409"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747929076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747929076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747929945","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747929945"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747930176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747930175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747930953","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747930953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747931815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747931814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747932904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747932903"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747933926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747933926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKWENDA"," userResponse":" TUTAKWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747934854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747934853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747935918","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747935918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUNUA"," userResponse":" KUNUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747936332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747936332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" SARE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747936966","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747936966"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747937143","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747937143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747937728","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747937728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mama ya Ebei alisema Kesho tutakwenda mjini kununua sare yako ya shule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747940943","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747940942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EBEI"," userResponse":" EBEI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747942107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747942107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFURAHI"," userResponse":" ALIFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747942837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747942837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ebei alifurahi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747946148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747946148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGESAFIRIA"," userResponse":" ANGESAFIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747946763","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747946763"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747947193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747947192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747947701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747947701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747948191","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747948191"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747948406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747948406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747949100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747949100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angesafiria katika ile basi kubwa ya buluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BULUU"," userResponse":" BULUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747951961","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747951961"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747952554","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747952554"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747953078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747953077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747953337","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747953336"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747953429","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747953429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747959910","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747959910"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747968363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747968363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543747977753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543747977753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748115455","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748115454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 11cab655-164b-4f0d-baef-b66e790ca864"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hakuweza kulala usiku huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748115563","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748115563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" aa69ec31-2715-4c2c-b33e-feaadf846b93"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_22"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na badala ya kumetameta na kuwa mrembo kama Mjusi alikuwa na sura mbaya zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748126159","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748126159"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748127250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748127250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748132034","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748132034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748133074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748133074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748139372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748139372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748140459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748140459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748145995","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748145995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748147035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748147035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748150823","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748150823"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748151870","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748151870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748158188","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748158188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748159238","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748159238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748161717","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748161716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748163364","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748163364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748176130","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748176130"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748177188","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748177188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748181578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748181577"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748182638","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748182638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748188174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748188174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748189231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748189230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748193134","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748193134"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748194175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748194174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748197197","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748197197"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748198254","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748198254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748208039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748208039"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748209075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748209075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748213350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748213350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748214386","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748214386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748217114","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748217114"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748218156","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748218156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748224750","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748224750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748225829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748225828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748230155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748230155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748231202","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748231202"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748234704","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748234704"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748235760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748235760"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748238449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748238449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748239514","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748239514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748242469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748242469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748244273","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748244273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748247013","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748247013"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748247084","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748247084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748248112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748248112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748249664","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748249664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748251691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748251690"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748251815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748251815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" fc4152e5-ab75-4130-9e94-476c0a5815b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748262115","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748262115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748263158","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748263158"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748267984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748267984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748269048","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748269048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748272560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748272560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748272813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748272812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" b37be356-f9fc-4a05-98c7-2656f9876504"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748284456","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748284456"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748289357","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748289357"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_7-8-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748294764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748294764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-7-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748302874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748302874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-1-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748308252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748308251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748314932","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748314932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-9-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748320459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748320459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-3-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748326032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748326032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-3-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748331636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748331636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-8-1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748337701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748337701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-8-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748343899","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748343898"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-8-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748352238","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748352238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-8-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748548677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748548673"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ae078350-59bf-47d9-acdb-1d9a04030970"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.30"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_5-8-0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748548779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748548777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9b455191-95ef-4298-b7fc-872d8f95b00e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" MASHUHURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748557701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748557700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 9b455191-95ef-4298-b7fc-872d8f95b00e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_23"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748579092","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748579092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748586601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748586601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748593263","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748593263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748599904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748599904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748606586","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748606586"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748613253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748613253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748619912","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748619912"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748626562","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748626561"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748634087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748634087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748643207","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748643207"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748649903","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748649903"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_2_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748656572","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748656572"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_1"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748663241","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748663241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748664790","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748664787"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 6643b744-3173-495b-976b-6afd1fc0978b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_7_4_0"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748676266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748676266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748684971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748684971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748686585","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748686585"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748691766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748691766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" START_KIBOKO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748694376","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748694376"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748695941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748695940"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748701705","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748701705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748703272","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748703272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748707259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748707258"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOMBE"," userResponse":" KOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748708867","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748708867"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" KILIMANJARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748716537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748716537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kilimanjaro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIMANJARO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748718112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748718112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748724175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748724175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748725740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748725740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748735640","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748735640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAA"," userResponse":" KAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748737224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748737224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748741182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748741181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kofia"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748742760","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748742760"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" KITENGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748746249","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748746249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitenge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITENGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748747839","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748747839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748752156","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748752156"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kobe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748753714","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748753714"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" KITUNGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748757270","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748757270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITUNGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748758831","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748758831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748763290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748763289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748764844","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748764844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748769519","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748769519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748771089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748771089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748776868","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748776868"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHWA"," userResponse":" KICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748778463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748778463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748782678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748782677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" START_KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748788954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748788954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kutembea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748790567","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748790567"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" KITAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748797076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748797076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitambaa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITAMBAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748798649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748798649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748803793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748803793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" START_KAROTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748805812","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748805812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748811917","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748811917"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748817309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748817309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748818913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748818913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748827105","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748827105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kikombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748828695","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748828695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748832537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748832537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIKO"," userResponse":" KIJIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748834103","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748834103"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" KALAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748842286","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748842286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kalamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748843900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748843899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748848703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748848703"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748850299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748850299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" KINU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748854015","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748854015"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748855648","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748855647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748858712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748858711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" katikati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748860288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748860288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" KUCHAKURO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748866516","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748866515"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuchakuro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHAKURO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748868216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748868216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748874861","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748874861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwaheri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748876431","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748876430"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748881100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748881099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748882683","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748882683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748886313","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748886313"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748887872","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748887872"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" KUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748894322","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748894322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kundi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748895882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748895882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" KIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748901277","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748901277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-K.rand.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748903290","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748903289"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748903466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748903465"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPEPEO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748914027","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748914026"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 164ec07f-8ccf-4565-bfb7-443df00e4468"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-K.rand.50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kipepeo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748923476","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748923476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_m-k-s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748926737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748926736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_f-k-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748929845","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748929845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-j-k"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748937966","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748937966"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-j-k"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748941432","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748941432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_s-k-n"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748949133","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748949133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_s-k-n"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748952628","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748952628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-g-a"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748955740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748955740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-l"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748958635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748958635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-g-n"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748961851","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748961851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_l-w-k"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748965662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748965661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-k-d"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748973563","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748973563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_o-k-d"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748977150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748977150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_u-d-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748982972","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748982971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" ce9b10b5-429a-4be5-b29a-195cdf5d45f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_K..K.all.rand.all.stat.show.98"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_k_u-d-k"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543748995549","data":{"timestamp":" 1543748995549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749000225","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749000225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-0-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749005651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749005651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-1-9"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749010239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749010238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-7-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749015405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749015405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_9-4-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749020643","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749020643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749025488","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749025488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-5-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749030531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749030531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-4-5"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749035734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749035733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-9-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749040534","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749040534"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-9-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543749047095","data":{"timestamp":" 1543749047094"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_100743"," gameId":" 91c35c12-4c3c-4251-9aab-17f6ab47f756"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2s.AV.mc.37"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-9-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}